{
    "id": "716d18f0c3de4447ab4e7a3a96c23201",
    "title": "Change The Voice",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have completed the work. / The work ........................... by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "completed",
                "is completed",
                "has completed",
                "has been completed"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "f955e697ccae4cfa817a7c2792e75c6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody has let the cat in. / The cat ........................... let in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has been",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e382fab1ae984ff5b8239a90291e26eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "We may win the match. / The match ........................... by us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may be win",
                "may have won",
                "may be won"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b125551037f4205863314a3aabf7d6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not insult the weak. / Let the weak ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not insult",
                "not be insulted",
                "not insulted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d42d51f89924d48af4dbd848abaac1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The nurse is looking after the patient. / The patient ......................... after by the nurse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is looking",
                "is being looked",
                "is looked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6372ada8e0a54516be781be53cb62f3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy is feeding the sparrows. / The sparrows .......................... by the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are fed",
                "are being fed",
                "have been fed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7c6b60c1877c4fce88d4afc57b9b4845"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our army has defeated the enemy.  / The enemy ................ by our army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is being defeated",
                "has been defeated",
                "is defeated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "386cefa3cd24481591bfe2ebe5e59904"
        },
        {
            "question": "One should keep oneâ€™s promises. / One's promises ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should keep",
                "should kept",
                "should be kept"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c1c0d4c260ef4516a691f7223fbddc99"
        },
        {
            "question": "They offered me a job. / I ........................ a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am offered",
                "was offered",
                "have been offered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9734c0c2083a408398a2bf02ca76823b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The engineers located the fault in the machine. / The fault in the machine ........................... by the engineers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is located",
                "was located",
                "has been located"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c1db1944f73495d88ee3e89a236def4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody could do anything. / Nothing could .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "done",
                "be done"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "315feb298c494564bb0510cdb157c64a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised at his behavior. / His behavior ...................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has surprised",
                "surprised",
                "had surprised"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61fc3b2a049b475dbbfdf3d97abb38ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Open the door. / Let the door .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "open",
                "be opened",
                "be open"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "143c6105ef3b499681f8356be0176f9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "His enemies killed him. / His enemies ....................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "killed",
                "killing",
                "have killed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8220dfded7844372b33842b597fba8a6"
        }
    ]
}